



Determination

Set Up Objectives

Decision Making

Public Speaking





Making Mobile Applications Based Database



Microsoft Office 2013



Mikrotik Certification





Indonesia



English



- Jl. Kauman, Ngabar Kraton, Pasuruan
- github.com/bud1purwanto budi.purwanto15@gmail.com
- Budi Purwanto
- 085233233770

CURRICULUM VITAE

BUDI PURWANTO, S.Tr.Kom

Informatics Engineering of State Polytechnic of Malang



Self Description

I am able to work under pressure, work in a team or individually, I really like working with many people and also able to handle many people when they have problems regarding office work matters or not. And lastly, I care about the people I work with. I think I have adequate education and work experience. Besides, I'm always enthusiastic about what I do. This will make a positive contribution to the company's growth.



PERSONAL INFO

Name : Budi Purwanto

Place of Birth : Pasuruan

Date of Birth : January 16, 1997

Gender : **Male**Religion : **Islam**



EDUCATION

2015-2019 Politeknik Negeri Malang

D4-Teknik Informatika

IPK 3.64



EXPERIENCE

Work Experience PT. Trias Sentosa, Tbk.

2019 - Present SAP ABAP Developer SQL Developer Organization Experience Lembaga Pers Mahasiswa Kompen

2017-2018 Member



SKILL & EXPERTISE

Design
Video Editing
MS. Word
MS. Excel

SAP ABAP

SQL Server

PHP

JavaScript

Java Mobile

BUDI PURWANTO

Pasuruan, East Java · 0852-3223-3770

budi.purwanto15@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/bud1purwanto · @bud1purwanto

A bachelor degree of majoring in Information Technology from State Politechnic of Malang. I am able to work under pressure, work in a team or individually, I really like working with many people and also able to handle many people when they have problems regarding office work matters or not. And lastly, I care about the people I work with. I think I have adequate education and work experience. Besides, I'm always enthusiastic about what I do. This will make a positive contribution to the company's growth.

EXPERIENCE

2019 SEPTEMBER-NOW

SR. ABAP DEVELOPER, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

I'm working with ERP software named SAP (System Application and Processing) as SAP ABAP Developer. As a SAP ABAP Developer, I am responsible to created or provided by SAP's internal functional consultant based on RICEF or functional specification, I write code using the ABAP programming language until it becomes a program that can be used.

Job Desc:

- SAP Business Improvement Full Life Cycle, develop the program according to the WRICEF.
- Liaise with functional to meet business requirements.
- Optimization code for handling huge data.
- Create technical design.
- Help functional team to investigate stories about standard transaction.
- Develop and maintain SAP FICO, MM, PM, PP, QM and SD
- ABAP Skills: BDC, BAPI, BAdI, Smartforms, etc.
- Debug and SQL trace to solve issues.
- Interfacing Download SAP to Other Platform.

List Project that I Participated:

• 2023 JANUARY- PRESENT

TTE SLIT ROLL INSPECTION AND TRACEABILITY, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have responsibility as SAP ABAP whose job is to do development programs to simplify transactions for QM Module (Result Recording, Usage Decision) in TTE Company (Using BAPI or BDC).

2022 JULY – 2022 DECEMBER

DIGITAL BOARDROOM, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have responsibility to do development programs SD Module to display data based on the RICEF that has been created, where the data is GP data from our company.

2022 JANUARY – 2022 AUGUST

SAP & NON-SAP IMPLEMENTATION FOR CPP#1 & OPP#7, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have responsibility to do program development in PP Module where I create a more dynamic program concept because the previous program required to make program changes (static) every time there are new production line implemention.

2022 APRIL – 2022 JUNE

REPORT CAPITAL EXPENDITURES (CAPEX), PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have responsibility to do development programs FICO Module for the costs incurred by the company to purchase, maintain and repair fixed assets/long-term assets.

• 2021 SEPTEMBER – 2022 AUGUST

BUSSINESS ANALYTICS (OLAP 2.0) - PRODUCTION REPORT, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have responsibility to do development program MM and PP to display prodution data to be downloaded to SQL and displayed to Power BI.

2021 MARCH – 2021 AUGUST

BUSSINESS ANALYTICS (OLAP 2.0) - SALES REPORT, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have responsibility to do development program SD Module to display sales and GP data to be downloaded to SQL and displayed to Power BI.

2020 SEPTEMBER – 2021 MARCH

REPORT SUBCONTRACTING INTERCOMPANY, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have responsibility as SAP ABAP whose job is to do development programs to simplify transactions MM Module for Inter Company (Using BAPI or BDC).

2019 OCTOBER- NOW

SQL DEVELOPER, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this company, I'm alsi working as SQL Developer. I write code using SQL programming language with SSMS (SQL Server Management Studio) on-demand to help them get some coherent data.

List Project that I Participated:

2019 NOVEMBER- 2020 MARCH

WASTE MANAGEMENT SYSTEM, PT. TRIAS SENTOSA.TBK

In this project, I have the responsibility to do development programs to conduct transactions and report company waste data (Table, View and Stored Procedure).

2018 AUGUST - 2018 SEPTEMBER

INTERN, PT. PELABUHAN INDONESIA III (PERSERO)

PT Pelabuhan Indonesia (Persero) is a company engaged in logistics, especially port management and development. In this project, I have the responsibility to develop a website program to manage the company's assets.

EDUCATION

2015 SEPTEMBER - 2019 JULY

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY, STATE POLYTECHNIC OF MALANG

Bachelor of Information Technology

SKILLS

- Strong sense of responsibility
- Eager to Learn
- Adaptive
- Communicative
- Have the same strength Individual or Team Work

- Analyze and Design Information System
- SAP ABAP
- SQL Developer
- Bussiness Analytic
- Design